[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "No  triangle is car, all  figures are  triangles",
        "answer": "No car is  figure",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All cars are  figures",
            "Some cars are  figures",
            "Some cars are not  figures"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "All squares are  rectangles, no  rectangle is  square",
        "answer": "No square is  square",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All squares are  squares",
            "Some squares are  squares",
            "Some squares are not  squares"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "All equilaterals are  squares, no  rectangle is  square",
        "answer": "No equilateral is  rectangle",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All equilaterals are  rectangles",
            "Some equilaterals are  rectangles",
            "Some equilaterals are not  rectangles"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "All squares are  rectangles, no  rectangle is  circle",
        "answer": "No square is  circle",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All squares are  circles",
            "Some squares are  circles",
            "Some squares are not  circles"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "All equilaterals are  squares, all  squares are  rectangles",
        "answer": "Some equilaterals are  rectangles",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All equilaterals are  rectangles",
            "No equilateral is  rectangle",
            "Some equilaterals are not  rectangles"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "All rectangles are  squares, no  triangle is  square",
        "answer": "No rectangle is  triangle",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All rectangles are  triangles",
            "Some rectangles are  triangles",
            "Some rectangles are not  triangles"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "No  square is bear, all  rectangles are  squares",
        "answer": "No bear is  rectangle",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All bears are  rectangles",
            "Some bears are  rectangles",
            "Some bears are not  rectangles"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "No mammal is  dog, all  mammals are  dogs",
        "answer": "No mammal is  mammal",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All mammals are  mammals",
            "Some mammals are  mammals",
            "Some mammals are not  mammals"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "All squares are  rectangles, all  rectangles are  squares",
        "answer": "Some squares are  squares",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All squares are  squares",
            "No square is  square",
            "Some squares are not  squares"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "All employees are  mammals, no  mammal is  plant",
        "answer": "No employee is  plant",
        "wrong-answers": [
            "All employees are  plants",
            "Some employees are  plants",
            "Some employees are not  plants"
        ]
    }
]